exceltemplates.net 2012-12-23

# Excel Templates

**Exceltemplates.net Privacy Statement**

What follows is the Privacy Statement for Exceltemplates.net website.

Please read this statement regarding our website. If you have questions please ask us through our email.

**Ownership of Information**

Exceltemplates.net is collected and received all information from many sources in the internet to be shared freely to our reader. All excel files available in this website is copyright of its respective owners.

**Comments/Message Boards**

Exceltemplates.net website contain comment sections (a.k.a. message boards). We do not actively monitor these comments and the information on them is for entertainment purposes only. If we are alerted to something we deem inappropriate in any way, we may delete it at our discretion. We use email validation on most of our message boards in order to reduce “comment spam.” These email addresses will not be shared with any third party.

**Cookies**

Currently we assign cookies to our readers in order to save their preferences. This data is not shared with any third party. Accessing our websites is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies if you wish.

**Third Party Cookies**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google Privacy Policy").

**Traffic Reports**

Our industry-standard traffic reporting records IP addresses, Internet service provider information, referrer strings, browser types and the date and time pages are loaded. We use this information in the aggregate only to provide traffic statistics to advertisers and to figure out which features and editorials are most popular.

**Legal proceedings**

We will make every effort to preserve user privacy but Exceltemplates.net may need to disclose information when required by law.

**Business Transitions**

If Exceltemplates.net is acquired by or merges with another firm, the assets of our websites, including personal information, will likely be transferred to the new firm.

**Links**

Exceltemplates.net websites frequently link to other websites. We are not responsible for the content or business practices of these websites. When you leave our websites we encourage you to read the destination site’s privacy policy. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Exceltemplates.net

**Notification of Changes**

When Exceltemplates.net makes changes to this privacy policy we will post those changes here.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at info@exceltemplates.net.

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
